http://www.petali.com.au/privacy

1. We respect your privacy
Petali Poll Merino & White Suffolk’s respects your right to privacy and this policy sets out how we collect and treat your personal information.
“Personal information” is information we hold which is identifiable as being about you.
2. What personal information we collect
We may collect the following types of personal information from you:
credit card information
detailed information about the running of your business as required for our services
3. How we collect your personal information
We collect personal information from you in a variety of ways, including: when you interact with us electronically or in person; when you access our website or social media presence(s); and when we provide our services to you.
4. Use of your personal information
We use your information to provide our service(s) to you. We also use it to improve our service and to notify you of opportunities that we think you might be interested in.
We do not provide your information to third parties, except that we may provide your information to our business partners who assist us in the provision of our services to you.
We will not under any circumstances sell or rent your information to a third party.
5. Security of your personal information
We take reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However we are not liable for any unauthorised access to this information.
6. Access to your personal information
You can access, update or request the removal of your personal information by contacting us.
7. Policy Changes
Any changes to this privacy policy will be updated on this site.
Petali Mailing List
If you are a human and are seeing this field, please leave it blank.
Fields marked with an * are required
Contact
Martin & Cheryl OppenheimerPetali, Walcha, NSW 2354 Australia
